Data changed.
We 3 厲中
The group нет acka
while giving you a ride
I'm in... yes, yes, please... but you can love it... it's delicious.
I've just eaten a cross-section of a year's worth of this.
What is it?
I'm not hungry...
One more time!
I'm sorry. Thank you.
It's heavy!
It's not good to drink it in half.
Next one too!
Cross-sectional view of the food.
What's that?
Hmm? Finished?
Oh, just now.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Of course.
Can I come in here?
I've never seen this before.
It says, "Die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die, die.
"Die, die, die!
I didn't write anything dirty like that.
Die!
Is it on the audio now?
Is it on the tape?
Stop it!
Is it on the site?
The picture... it's not on there.
Oh, here it is.
Hi... you know... I always send you the poverty law.
Kanagawa Prefecture.
You know, bad-mouthing people.
That's enough with the foul language.
That's enough.
Enough! Enough!
Over here?
We're broadcasting.
We're not in a pub.
Enough!
I look forward to working with you again this week.
I look forward to working with you this week.
So...
Last week, I made my debut!
I'm Lion!
This is Rhea Nakajima.
It's been a week, and it's still fresh.
I'll always be fresh.
Maybe a year from now, maybe a hundred years from now, I'll still be fresh.
Leave it to me.
Let me be in charge of freshness!
This week's shift is Mai Mai Mai.
I'm counting on you.
I have a special treat for those of you who've been watching.
I'll tell you something.
I sang a song for the Mai Mai Mai this week.
And it was great.
It was so good!
I hope you'll enjoy it.
Please, please, please.
I want you all to see it.
I heard that her voice makes all men fall in love with her.
That's right.
Legendary
And a voice.
Thank you very much.
That's one of the things I've been thinking about.
Let's get to the recording.
Let's begin.
So, today is the 13th of April.
Today is the 13th of April.
Yeah, it doesn't really ring a bell at this point.
The 13th.
I'm not sure if you're familiar with the time zone for the level, like 11:00 p.m., so even if I told you today is such and such a day, there's only an hour or so left.
I'm not so sure about that.
I've been thinking about what day it is tomorrow, and tomorrow is the 14th.
I'm sure it's Thursday today, right?
I'll tell you about the weekend tomorrow, the 14th of April, which I've never heard of before, but it's called Orange Day.
I've never heard of Orange Day before, but it's the day to confess your love on Valentine's Day, not Valentine's Day.
One month after Valentine's Day, March 14th is White Day, a day to return the favor, and one month after that is April 14th, which is tomorrow.
Orange is the day to confirm the love between two people.
Boo boo!
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
I'm not saying it's okay to eat the oranges... oranges... or oranges... or oranges... or oranges... or oranges... or oranges...
I want to make it a day where we can send orange gifts to each other
I'm sure all the orange vendors want to make it a trend now.
I'm already aiming for it, so I'll see you tomorrow.
I'm sure you've heard that today, April 13th, is a historic day for coffee shops.
I've been shuffling through the coffee shop.
Yes, isn't it right? In 1888, the 21st year of Meiji era, the first coffee shop in Japan was established in Ueno, Tokyo.
The second floor of that coffee shop was a store that served coffee.
It was a coffee shop that served coffee on the second floor, and once they had a "billy-out" or something like that.
That's how it started.
It started as a coffee shop heat, like when you get tired of playing downstairs, let's have tea upstairs.
Unlike today, coffee was a very expensive commodity back then.
No, no, no, I'll be the first one to drink it.
You'd better clean up the billiard table.
I'm sure you'll have a lot of days ahead of you today and tomorrow, so let's hear your news.
I'll tell you about Bircher's... this is the Liar... and it can work with computers and stuff...
I'm looking at the computer all the time.
Yeah. The size of the room is a little weird.
We're both big, and Maema is a little...
Buber... Buber...
Buber Shi If you put it this way, you're already a giant of progress!
Bubershi... I was 5'9" and 9 Titans too.
5'9" and 6'9" and 9 Titans... right?
Why don't you tell us why you're here too... let's hear from you...
I'm having trouble with my legs.
It's refreshing to read something like that from you, Mr. Liar.
I don't know what to do. Don't read anything bad about me.
There's a guy the same height as me.
I'm so happy... over 180, you feel like a big guy.
I think we'll be exterminated in the comments section.
There's one around here.
huh?
By the way, two of them are also taller than the average height of Japanese men.
I heard that the average height of Japanese boys used to go up and up and up until a while ago.
I heard that it's recently calmed down.
I think it was around 173? The average height for boys is now...
Wow, 173 for sure.
How about you, Master?
77.
77, so a little above average.
And you, Rhea... you're a Titan of Progress.
I'm the Climbing Titan.
I'm going to use my stereostat to get into his chest...
Go ahead! I'm like...
I'm going to spin around like Levi!
I don't think I'd be able to do that if I used the stereostatic device, though, given my height.
I'm sure...
I'd have to stick it in a place like that.
Absolutely impossible. I'd rather do it this way.
Mr. Devilucci
Sagamihara City Minami Ward
Erudite master
Refreshing Kaji
Hello, dainty Ebichu-chan!
When I went to a candy store in my neighborhood for the first time in a while
I found Moroccan yogurt, which I loved as a child.
Master!
He told me that they have big size yogurt now, so I asked him if it was Moroccan yogurt.
Can you take a look at the picture?
Can you look at the picture?
Wait a minute.
They used to sell them at candy stores.
Yes.
Like a hit or miss.
Oh, yeah, the ones that are scattered.Yes, yes, the ones that are scattered.
This is the one with the lid off, and you can eat it.
It's huge!
They have big size now.
They sell this size?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm sure, but this is a yogurt, isn't it?
That's right.
It's a yogurt, isn't it?
It's not yogurt, is it?
That's right.
It's a little sweet and sour on the inside, but it's not yogurt.
It's not yogurt or anything.
That's right.
I was so shocked when I found out as an adult.
I thought I was eating yogurt.
It's not yogurt or anything.
Yes, it is.
Have you ever had this hit?
What?
Have you ever had a hit?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, me neither. Have you?
No. Do you think you've won one of those?
Yes, they are.
Have any of you ever won?
Is there?
Maybe some yogurls have won.
I don't think so.
What's that? Yatter Noodles.
Yatter Noodles?
Something about the same price as a dime.
Something like that.
Like Baby Star Ramen.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's really hit or miss.
Moroccan yogurt is something I...
I thought maybe the lady at the candy store
I thought maybe the lady at the candy store was hiding all the winners.
That's how much I didn't get.
It's that hard to win.
It's that hard to get a hit.
You can always blame the store.
I'm the same way.
I thought you said you didn't have one of these.
It's like, "Auntie, what's up?
That's what I said.
It's a 20% chance of being set.
What?
A 20% chance of winning.
Then I'll get one this afternoon.
I see.
Then the odds are pretty high.
I don't remember ever winning a yogurt.
That's great, but there are people who have won.
Quite a few.
For example...
Does it say who it's for?
Yes.
It says "1978.
1978.
Excellent.
Ayaka.
Ayaka!
You're more of a jump serializer.
Sekino-san, I've hit on you too.
There's quite a few
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
So...
Since this happened...
I did some research.
I thought it was just a thing of the past.
I thought yogurt was a thing of the past.
But there are still 60,000 or 70,000 of them every day.
That much?
That's why it's probably being sold somewhere.
So it's probably being sold somewhere.
And of course there are people who buy it.
That's right.
That's true.
It's true that I don't see many butaishiya itself anymore.
I don't see them anymore.
Yes, that's true.
It's sad, isn't it?
No, no, no, no, no, no...
This is definitely amazing... the moment I think about it
Now that I look at it...
It's not yogurt or anything.
That's for sure.
What's Morocco?
Morocco is in Africa, right?
Yes.
It's on the Mediterranean Sea.
North of the Mediterranean.
The Mediterranean?
Morocco.
Oh, yeah.
That's that way.
That's up in Africa.
That's right.
And on the other side, the Mediterranean Sea, like Europe.
Like Italy.
Or France.
I think it's in that area.
Yogurt has nothing to do with it.
I've never heard of it.
I hear it's a big hit and a mystery wrapped in a mystery.
I hope you'll tell me you'll want to eat it.
Well, well, well... that's why I think it's art, isn't it?
Let's see what you can do with it today.
Creatures...
Creatures, creatures, survive!
The Osaka version of the marauding giants... in Kansai dialect... will survive...
You'll have to watch the movie to understand what he's saying.
So let's see... we received another shipment today...
Thank you.
A genius master. - Yes?
You weren't a genius even when you were in there.
You're a genius even when you're in there, you're not a genius, you little yellow-green idiot.
Good evening, yellow-green moron!
Good evening, and welcome to the Creature Creation Corner.
This time, the creature's name is "Dumbass, Dumbass, Dumbass.
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid!
I'll tell you what it is, so I'll call it Paca Paca.
I wonder what it is, so I pakapaka... This is a Hawaiian word, by the way.
I guess it's not the same in Japan...
Buber, it's a cute little Hawaiian word.
I'm a Kamehameha!
I think they're all about the laughs, right?
But over there, there are people who have heard of something really cool.
I'm sure that Leia, who's on the air right now, will give you the answer to that question you don't know the answer to.
I don't know the answer to that question.
I'd like a hint.
I'm not in the land.
I'm not in the land...
But not on land, so...
Silly paca...
Silly Paca
Well, however...
You're really good at drawing, aren't you?
Paca-paca
oh, paka paka
Oh, it's true, everyone seemed to think it was a horse, a horse.
That's what it is, isn't it?
By the sound.
I love Hawaiian language. Sounds like fun.
I can do a lot of things with this kind of groove.
I'm going to try to go to the front first.I'll go to the front first.
oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'm sure you've heard of this mysterious fish in Hawaii...
The mouth and the tip of the mouth are elongated and have a mysterious coloration.
Boo-boo!
Boo-boo-boo!
I heard that the Titan is also passed on by eating....
I'm sure that the Titan is also passed on by eating.
I'm sure you've heard of it before, right?
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get him to talk...
I wonder if its legs are a little strange...
I thought it was a shadow... but it looks like it's standing up...
I'm sure it's warm in Hawaii.
I'm not sure if it's the same here... but in Japan, it's more like...
It's a fish like this in Thailand.
what's pakapaka? what's pakapaka?
I'll have to ask someone from Hawaii about this... it's a fish, isn't it?
By the way, the thick milk is good for tomorrow, too.
I'm having an illustration done.
Okay, one time.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, it's just an ordinary fish...
I'm sorry, it's just a fish, or a fish and a fish, or a fish and a fish, or a fish and a fish, or a fish and a fish.
I'm sure tomorrow you'll be able to write "yellow-green idiot" or "yellow-green idiot" or "kmd" for short.
I'm sorry, I just posted this because I thought maybe you would write something about a horse with a long tail.
I'm sorry about this, but it's pretty close to what you wrote before.
I should have erased this. It was close, but... if you were my sister, you would have written this.
What? That's funny.
If you have any ideas about the creature, please send them to us.
Yes...
Well then, how about the distribution?
I'm sure you're right... who is that white Kenken?
I've never seen him before in Hawaii.
I see...
Is there anything else?
You're almost right, Mayama
You're almost right
Well, well, well
But this isn't a corner where you get it right
It's a corner where you get it right
That's a good type, isn't it?
Well, well, well.
Okay, Duncan, you're on the air.
I hope to see you all next week.
Thank you very much for your time this week.
Can I ask you to close the front door, too?
Yes, ma'am.
That's it for this week.
It's like "Donden-donden"?
Showa
Okay, see you all next week.
Thank you very much.
Yes, that's the end.
Thank you for your hard work.